DETECTIVE: Thanks for coming in, Mr. Hale. Just routine.
HALE: You said on the phone it was about the Briar Park case.
DETECTIVE: That's right. Do you know why we're talking to you?
HALE: Because I live two blocks from the park. Like a lot of people.
DETECTIVE: A woman was found there last Sunday. Margaret Vale.
HALE: I read about it in the paper.
DETECTIVE: We pulled traffic cam footage from Briar and Eleventh.
DETECTIVE: Your car passes that intersection at 6:42 a.m.
HALE: I jog in that area. That's not new information.
DETECTIVE: Mr. Hale, you don't jog. You drove.
HALE: Sometimes I drive to the trailhead and then I jog.
DETECTIVE: At 6:42 a.m. on a Sunday. Same time she died.
HALE: I didn't know what time she died. The paper didn't say.
DETECTIVE: That's because we never released the time.
HALE: I — I assumed. People assume things.
DETECTIVE: Did you know Margaret Vale, Mr. Hale?
HALE: No. I told the officer outside that already.
DETECTIVE: Then can you explain this photograph?
DETECTIVE: It was on her phone. Taken six weeks ago. You and her.
HALE: That's — that's a community fundraiser.
HALE: We were both there. Doesn't mean we knew each other.
DETECTIVE: She had your number written on the back of the print.
HALE: I want a lawyer.
DETECTIVE: That's your right. Before you make that call,
DETECTIVE: I need to tell you something we found.
DETECTIVE: There was a letter in her apartment.
DETECTIVE: It was addressed to her brother.
DETECTIVE: She had been looking for him for thirty-one years.
DETECTIVE: She found him last spring. We pulled DNA from a coffee cup.
HALE: I don't — I don't understand.
DETECTIVE: Mr. Hale, did your mother put you up for adoption in 1992?
HALE: How did you —
DETECTIVE: She wrote you a letter. Margaret. Your sister.
DETECTIVE: She wanted to meet you. Properly. Last Sunday.
DETECTIVE: At 6:30 a.m. At the trailhead.
HALE: I didn't — I didn't know.
DETECTIVE: Didn't know what, Mr. Hale?
HALE: I went there. I went there to meet her.
HALE: She wasn't there. There was a man.
HALE: He was leaving. He had a bag. I didn't see his face.
DETECTIVE: A man was leaving the trailhead at 6:42.
DETECTIVE: And you didn't think to mention this to anyone?
HALE: I — I didn't know who she was. To me.
HALE: I drove home. I told myself it was nothing.
DETECTIVE: Mr. Hale, can you describe the man you saw?
HALE: Tall. Limping. He was limping on his left side.
DETECTIVE: One more question. The lawyer can wait.
DETECTIVE: When did you find out she was your sister?
HALE: Two minutes ago. Just now.
HALE: She just wanted to meet me. And I left.
DETECTIVE: Mr. Hale, I'm going to need you to stay.
DETECTIVE: Not as a suspect. As the only witness we have.